const qBank = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "Which sport’s tournament is known as the European Club Cup of Champions?",
		options: ["Tennis", "Badminton", "Squash", "Table Tennis"],
		answer: "Table Tennis",
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: "In which Summer Olympics, Badminton was introduced for the first time?",
		options: ["1992", "1996", "2000", "2004"],
		answer: "1992",
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: "Where was the first Winter Olympics held?",
		options: ["Greece", "France", "Germany", "England"],
		answer: "France"
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "Where are the headquarters of the Olympic Council of Asia?",
		options: ["New Delhi", "Singapore", "Kuwait City", "Seoul"],
		answer: "Kuwait City"
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "Which sport’s scoring format is “Par and Bogey”?",
		options: ["Tennis", "Golf", "Badminton", "Cricket"],
		answer: "Golf"
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question: "Which sport’s competition is known as the “National Pro Fastpitch”?",
		options: ["Basketball", "Baseball", "Softball", "Netball"],
		answer: "Softball"
	},
    {
		id: 7,
		question: "What is the normal time difference between which both the Summer Olympics and Winter Olympics are held?",
		options: ["1 Year", "2 Years", "4 Years", "None of the above"],
		answer: "2 Years"
	},
	
	{
		id: 8,
		question: "Jeev Milkha Singh is associated with which sports?",
		options: ["Volleyball", "Hockey", "Golf", "Athletics"],
		answer: "Golf"
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: "How many players are there in Kabbadi team?",
		options: ["11", "7", "21", "None of the above"],
		answer: "7"
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: "Which of the following games is not included in the Olympic Games?",
		options: ["Skiing", "Cycling", "Cricket", "Archery"],
		answer: "Cricket"
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: "'Ashes' is the term associates with which sports?",
		options: ["Basketball", "Hockey", "Football", "Cricket"],
		answer: "Cricket"
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: "The term 'Butterfly Stroke' is associated with",
		options: ["Wrestling", "Swimming", "Boxing", "Kabaddi"],
		answer: "Swimming"
	},
	{
		id: 13,
		question: "2016 olymics was held at _______________ .",
		options: ["Los Angeles", "Tokyo", "Paris", "Rio de Janeiro"],
		answer: "Rio de Janeiro"
	},
	{
		id: 14,
		question: "Who won the most gold medals in Asian Games?",
		options: ["India", "China", "Japan", "None of the above"],
		answer: "China"
	},
	{
		id: 15,
		question: "How many medals has India won in Asian Games 2022?",
		options: ["32", "383", "107", "78"],
		answer: "107"
	},
	{
		id: 16,
		question: "Which Asian country has hosted the Asian Games the most times?",
		options: ["Thailand", "South Korea", "China", "India"],
		answer: "Thailand"
	},
	{
		id: 17,
		question: "Which is considered the national sports of India?",
		options: ["Chess", "Hockey", "Cricket", "Water Polo"],
		answer: "Hockey"
	},
	{
		id: 18,
		question: "How many players are there on a baseball team?",
		options: ["12", "11", "5", "9"],
		answer: "9"
	},
	{
		id: 19,
		question: "What sport is considered the “king of sports”?",
		options: ["Soccer", "Volleyball", "Squash", "Badminton"],
		answer: "Soccer"
	},
	{
		id: 20,
		question: "What water sport can be played by up to 20 people in a team?",
		options: ["Dragon boat racing", "Swimming", "Water Polo", "Ice hockey"],
		answer: "Dragon boat racing"
	},
	{
		id: 21,
		question: "What is water hockey’s alternative name?",
		options: ["Ice hockey", "Octopush", "Cliff diving", "Windsurfing"],
		answer: "Octopush"
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		question: "Where is the largest bowling centre located?",
		options: ["US", "Japan", "Singapore", "Finland"],
		answer: "Japan"
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		question: "Where did the term “billiard” originated from?",
		options: ["Italy", "Hungary", "India", "France"],
		answer: "France"
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		question: "What is the maximum break in snooker?",
		options: ["147", "207", "96", "134"],
		answer: "147"
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		question: "What is the name of the person that controls a football match?",
		options: ["A referee", "An umpire", "A goalkeeper", "A spectator"],
		answer: "A referee"
	},
]

export default qBank;
